plomedia.com 2010-11-19

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

#### Information AdaMide.com Collects

Certain information is collected from you upon entering your email on our site. 

AdaMide.com does utilize the service of cookies to help us enhance the experience of our website. These cookies are used to track the visits our site is getting and to help us collect information about our users

#### How We Use This Information

Any information AdaMide.com collects will be used in one of the following ways:   

  * To help us deliver an experience that is more personalized   
(With this information, we can better respond to individual needs)
  * To assist us with making improvement to customer service   
(We will be able to more effectively respond to your support needs and requests)
  * To help us promote the site through surveys, contests and other new features
  * To help us keep contact with you by email 

Note: You will receive detailed instructions on how to unsubscribe from further AdaMide.com emails in the event you would like to unsubscribe. You will find the details at the bottom of each email.

#### How AdaMide.com Protects Your Information

Upon accessing AdaMide.com, we have implemented a variety of security measures to make sure your personal information is kept safe.

#### Does AdaMide.com Use Cookies?

AdaMide.com does use cookies, which enables our site or your internet service provider to recognize which browsers are being used and help us retain certain information. This is done via a small file that the site or ISP will transfer to your computer� hard drive through your browser.

Cookies are used to help AdaMide.com get a better understanding of the preferences of our users, and help us save those preferences for future site visits. We also use them to help aggregate site traffic and interaction data, so we can continue to improve our site experience for future use.

#### Is Your Information Disclosed to Outside Parties?

Outside parties will never receive any personally identifiable information through sale, trade or other dispersal methods, from AdaMide.com. We do work with various third parties that assist us with our business operation, website operation, or marketing efforts, that are not included in these outside parties. These parties must agree to keep this information protected and confidential. If it is determined to be necessary to comply with the law or our privacy policy or terms of service, or to protect our rights or the rights of others, your information may be released. Information that is not personally identifiable may be provided to outside parties for marketing or advertising purposes.

#### Third Party Links

AdaMide.com may, at our discretion, offer third-party services or products on our website. Each of these third-party sites have independent privacy policies from those listed on this page. AdaMide.com retains no responsibility or liability for any activities or content related to these third-party sites. We do, however, welcome any feedback related to these sites, as we would like to protect our site and its integrity.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

All necessary steps required to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act have been taken by AdaMide.com. Your privacy is something that we value greatly. Your personal information will not be distributed to outside parties without your consent, in accordance with this act.

#### Children� Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We do not collect any information from anyone under the age of 13, in compliance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). DailyLife and all represented products and services are all directed at people who are at least 13 years of age or older.

In compliance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), AdaMide.com will never collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. All services and products featured on our website are intended for use of people that are at least 13 years old.

#### Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted to this page.
